(Sheldon:)Albert Einstein
never had a driver's license.
(Howard:)Yeah, but Albert Einstein didn't make me
wet myself at 40 miles an hour.
(Penny:)Yeah, and I never wanted
to kick Albert Einstein in the nuts.
(Penny:)You know, I gotta ask, why didn't you just
get a license at 16 like everybody else?
(Sheldon:)I was otherwise engaged.
(Penny:)Doing what?
(Sheldon:)Examining perturbative amplitudes
in N=4 supersymmetric theories...
(Sheldon:)...leading to a re-examination
of the ultraviolet properties...
(Sheldon:)...of multi-loop N=8 supergravity
using modern twistor theory.
Well, how about when you were 17?
(DMV Lady(to the person ahead of Sheldon in the queue):)Take this to the testing area.
Name at the top.
(DMV Lady(to the person ahead of Sheldon in the queue):)Sign the bottom, answer
the questions, bring it back. Next.
(DMV Lady(to the person ahead of Sheldon in the queue):)Application?
(Sheldon:)I'm actually more of a theorist.